One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
The Legendary Hero
Le Héros de la Légende
Big news!
Grosse nouvelle !
Beehive, the Pirate Island New World
La Ruche, l'Île des Pirates Nouveau Monde
Captain Koby has escaped!
Le colonel Kobby s’est évadé !
Seriously?!
Sérieux ?
He escaped, so he's not the commodore's prize anymore, right?!
S’il s’est tiré, l’amiral peut plus rien dire.
How much will we get if we capture him?!
Choper ce petit gars rapportera une fortune.
Well, we don't need to put a bounty on him!
Qui a mis sa tête à prix ? Sûrement pas nous.
Cross Guild will pay it for us!
C’est la Cross Guild qui paie.
I bought odds on him with a win ticket!
Je parie sur lui comme cheval, moi ! Kobby va rapporter gros !
How much will we get if we kill him?!
Et mort, il fera dans les combien ?
Wait till you hear this!
Ça va vous faire tout drôle.
He's a five-star bounty!
Une prime cinq étoiles.
That means five treasure chests! A total of 500 million berries!
On aura droit à cinq coffres au trésor, vers 500 Millions.
A five-star bounty?!
Une prime cinq étoiles ? Les colonels sont à une, d’habitude !
Alright! Let's hit the jackpot!
À nous la richesse facile !
Let the hunt begin!
Que la chasse commence !
I'm feeline a tickle on the left side of my chest.
Ça me chatouille du côté gauche de mon torse.
That's where the slaves are held before they're sold...
C’est là que sont les esclaves prévus pour la vente.
Are they breaking out?!
Ils sont en train de s’évader !
The slaves escaped?!
Les esclaves se font la malle ?
Can we hunt them, Pizarro?!
On a le droit de les chasser, Pizarro ?
Don't be stupid!
N’importe quoi, vous avez la rapine trop facile.
Bring them all back!
Ramenez-les-moi ! Et ne touchez pas un cheveu de Kobby.
or I'll tell Teach!
Je vais vous balancer à Teach.
Why is that mountain talking...?
Pourquoi le rocher parle ?
He knows that we're here!
Nous avons été repérés.
Let's hurry!
Dépêchons-nous.
What?
Quoi ?
This is it for us...
Nous n’irons pas plus loin.
Just run away before we slow you down.
Prenez la fuite, même seul. Nous ne voulons pas vous ralentir.
Don't give up hope.
Gardez toujours un espoir.
I'll lure them all away...
Je les attirerai ailleurs.
so make sure everyone escapes!
Profitez-en pour filer avant qu’ils vous rattrapent.
Well then...
Au revoir.
We'll meet again!
Nous nous reverrons !
Thanks!
Merci, colonel !
Thank you, Captain Koby...
Merci, colonel Kobby…
You're a saint!
Vous êtes un saint !
Shiryu of the Rain Clear-Clear Fruit Invisible Man
Shiryu de la Pluie Fruit de l'Invisibilité
You should have captured them yourself, Pizarro.
Attrape donc les fuyards toi-même, Pizzaro.
Like I said, Teach would be pissed.
Certainement pas, Teach va encore gueuler.
"Corrupt King" Avalo Pizarro Isle-Isle Fruit Island Man
Avalo Pizarro, "le Roi Dépravé" Fruit de l'Île
I just break things whenever I meowve.
Plein de trucs se cassent au moindre de mes mouvements.
Mind if I take a shot?
Et moi, je peux y aller ?
Vasco Shot... What are mew gonna do?
T’as d’autres idées stupides, Vasco Shot ?
They can't run if I burn down the town.
Si je mets le feu à la ville, ils seront tous coincés.
"Heavy Drinker" Vasco Shot Glug-Glug Fruit Booze Man
Vasco Shot, "Le Roi de la Bibine" Fruit du Glouglou
Hey, don't do that! That would be a meowssive fire!
N’y pense même pas, tu vas embraser toute l’île.
Teach would be furrious!
Teach va se mettre en rogne.
It's fine. Leave it to me.
C’est tranquille, flippe pas trop.
Furget it! We just finished fixing up Rocky Port!
Non ! Les réparations de Rocky Port sont à peine achevées !
Would you rather leave it to Wolf?
Tu préfères que ce soit Wolf qui s’en occupe ?
Wolf?
Wolf…
"Colossal Battleship" Sanjuan Wolf Huge-Huge Fruit Gigantification Man
Sanjuan Wolf, "Le Cuirassé Géant" Fruit du Gigantisme
That's meowt of the question!
Oublie-le, c’est encore pire.
Mew might as well just destroy the whole town!
Il va nous détruire toute la ville.
I found him!
Je l’ai trouvé !
Damn! I guess I can't outrun them!
Ça s’annonce mal, je ne leur échapperai pas.
Somehow...
Je dois tenir.
I have to keep them busy until everyone can escape to the sea!
Le temps que les autres puissent prendre la mer !
Koby the Hero!
Kobby le héros.
Koby the Hero, I want to turn this island...
Tu vois, Kobby le héros, je veux changer cette île.
this Pirate Island...
L’île des pirates…
into a full-fledged nation!
j’en ferai un vrai État à part entière.
A World Government-affiliated nation!
Un pays qui appartiendra au Gouvernement Mondial.
It'll be the Blackbeard Kingdom...
J’en serai le roi.
with me as its king!
Ce sera le royaume de Barbe Noire.
How's that?
T’en penses quoi ?
Stop this nonsense.
Cessez de dire des sottises.
There's no way it would work!
Personne ne l’acceptera jamais.
It'd be a country of criminals!
Un pays de criminels ?
Hey, don't step on a man's dream!
Gamin, ne gâche pas les rêves des gens.
I'll negotiate with them using you as a bargaining chip.
Je vais négocier leur reconnaissance en échange de ta vie.
If the government or the Marines give in to terrorists, we're all doomed!
Le Gouvernement et la Marine ne négocient pas avec les terroristes.
Anyway, you're wasting your time.
De toute façon, c’est impossible.
Because...
Puisque moi,
I'm a member of SWORD!
j’appartiens au Sword.
SWORD?
Au Sword ? C’est quoi, ce truc ?
Oh, I see...
Je vois.
This isn't gonna go well.
On en tirera rien.
Give up on the trade, Teach.
Oublie le marché, Teach.
What he means...
Ce gars-là,
is that he's a Marine but also not.
c’est un soldat sans en être un.
He gave up his Marine code.
Il a renoncé à son Code Marine.
SWORD is a group of Marines that have already submitted their resignations.
Avant d’appartenir au Sword,
Which means they could even fight the Four Emperors without permission.
Ils n’ont pas besoin de permission pour attaquer un Empereur.
They can operate however they choose and disregard any and all orders.
Ils sont libres de leurs mouvements et peuvent ignorer les ordres.
They're free agents.
C’est une unité autonome.
In exchange...
En contrepartie,
the Marines are in no way responsible for their actions...
la Marine n’assume aucune responsabilité pour leurs actions.
and can fire them anytime.
Ils peuvent les licencier à tout moment.
I see!
Tout est plus clair.
So there's the normal idiots who sit around waiting for permission,
D’où la différence avec les toutous dans les jupes de leur chef.
and you guys, who charge in without thinking twice!
C’est pour ça que ces gars foncent dans le tas.
Now that I get it, I like your style!
Ça me plaît pas mal, comme attitude.
But...
Par contre,
I'm not gonna change the plan!
je changerai pas de plan.
I'll do it anyway!
Je vais quand même tenter.
Even if you're in SWORD,
Même si tu viens du Sword,
the people still call you a hero.
la populace t’appelle le « héros ».
I wonder if the Marines can really afford to just abandon you.
Je doute que la Marine puisse te jeter facilement.
Let's ask the public, shall we?!
Je rendrai mon offre publique.
That way the government can't just wash their hands of this!
Si le Gouvernement refuse, sa popularité en prendra un coup.
Until then, lock him up!
En attendant, qu’il croupisse aux cachots.
I can't wait!
On va bien se marrer…
Don't let him escape!
Tenez-le bien à l’œil !
Get back here, Koby!
Reste là, Kobby !
I'll free you, so you're going to free Master Moria from his cell.
Je vais te sortir de là.
I may have cooperated with a pirate...
J’ai fait un pacte avec une pirate,
but you gotta do what you gotta do!
mais on a rien sans rien.
What's that?
Qui va là ?
Three Marines spotted at the port!
Trois soldats de la Marine repérés au port !
What? Marines?! No way!
Quoi ? Des soldats ? C’est une blague ?
Hurry up!
Grouillez-vous !
They're strong! Be careful!
C’est pas du menu fretin, faites gaffe.
Did someone come to rescue me?
Qui est venu à mon secours ?
No, no!
Non, c’est autre chose. Quelle arrogance !
I'm ashamed!
Je me fais honte.
Who are they?!
Qui c’est ? Ils sont trop forts !
They're heading toward the center of the town!
Ils vont vers le centre de l’île !
What do they want?!
Ils veulent quoi ?
Who cares?! Stop them!
On s’en tape. Arrêtez-les !
Guns don't work on them!
Nos flingues servent à rien…
That's as far as you go!
Je vais vous démolir !
He cut his head off!
Et une tête en moins !
I took one down!
J’en ai buté un.
That'll teach you!
Ça leur fera les pieds.
That hurt...
Ça fait mal…
A logia?!
Un Logia ?
What's with this guy?!
C’est qui, ce type ? On le dirait fait d’argile !
Where are you, Koby?!
Où tu te caches, Kobby ?
H-Hey...
Regardez…
Are those buildings moving?!
Les bâtiments bougeraient pas ?
No, stupid! Of course not!
N’importe quoi, faut y aller mollo sur la picole.
Go on! Be a good little boy!
C’est bien, gentils garçons…
Get a move on!
Foncez droit devant.
What a weird lady. Who is that?
Elle est pas nette, la gonzesse. Qui c’est ?
Come on, straighten up!
Allez, ça ne bouge pas assez, tout ça !
You look pathetic!
Ne faites pas cette tête de plouc.
Come on! Come on! Come on!
Du nerf, allez !
She's whipping a building...
Elle fouette le mur ?
What is it? Staring, are we?
Vous voulez ma photo, les soûlards ?
What? No, I...
Non, surtout pas…
S-She's a Marine?!
Elle est de la Marine ?
Is it that rare for a pirate to set eyes on a Marine?
Vous ne voyez pas souvent de soldats, les pirates d’eau douce ?
Rear Admiral Kujaku Marine Headquarters (SWORD) Granddaughter of "Master Tactician" Tsuru Whip-Whip Fruit Discipline Woman
Contre-amiral Kujaku QG de la Marine (SWORD) Petite-fille de Tsuru – Fruit du Fouet
Rear Admiral Kujaku Marine Headquarters (SWORD) Granddaughter of "Master Tactician" Tsuru Whip-Whip Fruit Discipline Woman
Contre-amiral Kujaku QG de la Marine (SWORD) Petite-fille de Tsuru – Fruit du Fouet
Rear Admiral Kujaku Marine Headquarters (SWORD) Granddaughter of "Master Tactician" Tsuru Whip-Whip Fruit Discipline Woman
Contre-amiral Kujaku QG de la Marine (SWORD) Petite-fille de Tsuru – Fruit du Fouet
Rear Admiral Kujaku Marine Headquarters (SWORD) Granddaughter of "Master Tactician" Tsuru Whip-Whip Fruit Discipline Woman
Contre-amiral Kujaku QG de la Marine (SWORD) Petite-fille de Tsuru – Fruit du Fouet
Rear Admiral Kujaku Marine Headquarters (SWORD) Granddaughter of "Master Tactician" Tsuru Whip-Whip Fruit Discipline Woman
Contre-amiral Kujaku QG de la Marine (SWORD) Petite-fille de Tsuru – Fruit du Fouet
Rear Admiral Kujaku Marine Headquarters (SWORD) Granddaughter of "Master Tactician" Tsuru Whip-Whip Fruit Discipline Woman
Contre-amiral Kujaku QG de la Marine (SWORD) Petite-fille de Tsuru – Fruit du Fouet
Rear Admiral Kujaku Marine Headquarters (SWORD) Granddaughter of "Master Tactician" Tsuru Whip-Whip Fruit Discipline Woman
Contre-amiral Kujaku QG de la Marine (SWORD) Petite-fille de Tsuru – Fruit du Fouet
Rear Admiral Kujaku Marine Headquarters (SWORD) Granddaughter of "Master Tactician" Tsuru Whip-Whip Fruit Discipline Woman
Contre-amiral Kujaku QG de la Marine (SWORD) Petite-fille de Tsuru – Fruit du Fouet
Rear Admiral Kujaku Marine Headquarters (SWORD) Granddaughter of "Master Tactician" Tsuru Whip-Whip Fruit Discipline Woman
Contre-amiral Kujaku QG de la Marine (SWORD) Petite-fille de Tsuru – Fruit du Fouet
Rear Admiral Kujaku Marine Headquarters (SWORD) Granddaughter of "Master Tactician" Tsuru Whip-Whip Fruit Discipline Woman
Contre-amiral Kujaku QG de la Marine (SWORD) Petite-fille de Tsuru – Fruit du Fouet
Rear Admiral Kujaku Marine Headquarters (SWORD) Granddaughter of "Master Tactician" Tsuru Whip-Whip Fruit Discipline Woman
Contre-amiral Kujaku QG de la Marine (SWORD) Petite-fille de Tsuru – Fruit du Fouet
Rear Admiral Kujaku Marine Headquarters (SWORD) Granddaughter of "Master Tactician" Tsuru Whip-Whip Fruit Discipline Woman
Contre-amiral Kujaku QG de la Marine (SWORD) Petite-fille de Tsuru – Fruit du Fouet
Come to me.
Venez me voir, mes mignons.
I'll whip you into shape.
Je vais vous dresser un coup.
You're cornered, Koby!
T’es cerné, Kobby !
Oh no! I'm surrounded!
Mince, ils m’encerclent…
Take aim!
En joue !
Is this it for me?
C’est fini pour moi…
On my mark!
Une seule salve !
Fire!
Feu à volonté !
It's beautiful!
C’est joli !
Wait, no!
Mais non ! C’est quoi, cette merde ?
Why did a flower come out of the muzzle?!
Pourquoi nos flingues tirent des fleurs ?
No, wait...
Attendez, les gars…
This is...
Je sais ce que c’est.
one of Dr. Vegapunk's inventions!
Une invention du Dr Végapunk,
It earned him the Mobel Peace Prize!
celle qui lui a valu le prix Ibel de la paix !
That's not what I'm asking!
C’était pas ma question !
Who did this?!
Qui a fait ça ?
Koby!
Colonel Kobby !
Get over here!
Venez dans mes bras !
Wait, no!
Euh, ne le prenez pas au pied de la lettre…
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Commander Hibari Marine Headquarters (SWORD)
Lieutenant Commandant Hibari QG de la Marine (SWORD)
Hibari! What are you doing here?!
Hibari ! Que fais-tu ici ?
Don't tell me...
C’est toi qui…
Yes!
Oui ! J’ai tiré des muni-fleurs droit dans leurs canons.
They can't use their weapons!
Leurs armes sont hors service, rejoignez-moi pendant ce temps.
A-And...
Et si jamais…
if you're hungry, I...
vous avez faim…
made...
je vous ai apporté…
lunch for you!
un bon repas !
Huh?
Pardon ?
No, I mean...
Laissez tomber.
Prince! Any progress?
Prince, du nouveau ?
Yeah, we just finished up here.
Je viens de finir le travail.
Rear Admiral Prince Grus
Sous-amiral Prince Gles QG de la Marine
Koby is safe, too!
Fruit de la Bouillasse Homme Argile
Glorp-Glorp Fruit
Kobby est sain et sauf.
Mud Puppet (Golem)
Marionnette de Boue (Golem)
Isn't that building moving?
Tu trouves pas que les bâtiments bougent ?
H-Hey, wait!
Attends !
O-Oh no...
C’est pas possible… On est enfermés là-dedans.
Now, whenever you're ready!
C'est quand vous voulez.
Head to the very center!
Foncez en plein milieu !
It's all ready!
Contact établi avec Prince.
Everyone, hang onto something!
À tout l’équipage, accrochez-vous.
Charge!
À l’assaut !
C'mon! Hurry up!
Hâtez-vous !
Let's get out of here!
Enfuyons-nous au plus vite !
Look up!
Regardez là-haut !
A Marine ship is flying through the sky!
Un navire de la Marine vole dans le ciel !
Why?! How is that possible?!
Comment c’est possible ?
Who's on it?!
Qui est à bord ?
Isn't it... falling toward us?
C’est moi, ou il est en chute libre ?
R-Run!
Déguerpissez !
Look!
Visez un peu la proue !
No way! I thought he retired!
Il avait pas pris sa retraite, lui ?
The legendary...
C’est le héros légendaire !
Vice Admiral Garp!
Le Vice-amiral Garp est là !
Koby!
Kobby ! Je suis venu à ta rescousse !
Run! Just run!
On se tire ! Cassez-vous tous !
We can't...
C’est fichu… La place est condamnée !
Hey, you damn pirates!
Salut, mes copains les pirates !
He's coming! Run!
Il arrive ! Fuyons !
Vice Admiral Garp...
Vice-amiral Garp…
Why? I'm not even worth saving...
Pourquoi êtes-vous venu pour moi ?
You idiots!
Aviez-vous bien conscience
Do you have any idea who the hell you've kidnapped?!
de qui est le petit bonhomme que vous avez enlevé ?
Koby is the future of the Marines!
Kobby est l’avenir de la Marine.
Not to mention...
Mais plus que ça,
my precious protégé!
il est avant tout mon disciple bien-aimé !
Galaxy...
Galaxy...
Impact!
Impact !
Cumulo-glorpus!
Argilo-nimbus !
Damn you, Garp!
Bon sang, ce sale Garp… Il est cinglé !
I'll make that geezer pay!
On va lui montrer, au vieux croûton !
Don't move, pirates!
Pas un geste, maudits pirates.
Resistance will only result in further damage!
Résister ne fera que plus de victimes dans vos rangs.
Absolutely pathetic...
C'est pas bon, ça…
I've really gotten rusty.
Je me suis rouillé.
Screw you!
Arrête ton cirque !
As if there's anything left to damage!
On ne va pas te laisser défoncer notre île.
Vice Admiral Garp!
Vice-amiral Garp !
Oh, Koby!
Salut, Kobby !
You're okay!
T’as rien de cassé ?
Thank goodness!
Sacré Kobby…
They didn't kill him!
J’avais tellement peur qu’on trouve sa dépouille…
Really now...
Garp n’y est pas allé de main morte.
You're such a naughty boy, Garp!
Quel vilain garnement !
Garp said Koby's the future of the Marines. I won't stand for it!
Kobby, l’avenir de la Marine ? Il va me le payer cher.
I'm gonna sabotage him!
Il me trouvera sur sa route.
That's something you're supposed to keep to yourself, you spoiled brat.
Les bâtons dans les roues, ça se met en douce, le fils à papa.
It's cuter that way.
Comme c’est mignon.
Koby!
Kobby !
Captain Koby!
Colonel Kobby !
Tashigi!
Tashigi…
Even non-SWORD members came...
Vous n’êtes même pas tous du Sword…
Hey, Koby! Why are you lugging that thing around?
Qu’est-ce que tu trimballes, Kobby ?
Vice Admiral Garp!
Vice-amiral Garp !
We've tried everything, but we can't get the shackle off!!
Impossible de retirer le boulet.
Please...
Faites quelque…
do...
chose…
some...
Que…
Hibari...!
Hibari !
Kuzan.
Kuzan.
Kuzan!
Monsieur Kuzan !
What are you doing?!
Qu’est-ce qui vous prend ? Délivrez Hibari sur-le-champ !
It's Aokiji!
C’est Aokiji !
Captain Kuzan!
Commandant Kuzan !
Kuzan!
Mon Kuzounet !
Don't get me in trouble, Koby.
Je suis bien embêté, Kobby.
I can't have you running off...
Tant que Teach ne sera pas là,
while Teach is away.
tu n’iras nulle part.
Two years ago, Admiral Akainu and Admiral Aokiji...
Deux ans plus tôt,
fought for the position of the next fleet admiral of Marine Headquarters.
D’un côté, l’Amiral Akainu.
The deadly struggle went on for ten days before a victor emerged:
Au terme d’une lutte fratricide qui dura dix longs jours,
Akainu.
Akainu l’emporta.
However, Aokiji refused to serve under him.
Aokiji refusa toutefois de servir sous Akainu
And so, he left the Marines.
et déserta la Marine.
Some Island, New World
Sur une certaine île, Nouveau Monde
What the...?!
Ma parole !
Blackbeard's here!
C’est Barbe Noire !
Run! Get out of the town!
Fuyez ! Quittez la ville !
Hey!
Hé !
What happened here?
Qu’est-ce qui se passe ici ?
Wait! Who did this?!
Restez là ! Dites-moi qui a fait ça !
No, I don't need to ask...
La question ne se pose même pas.
There's only one person in the world who could've done this!
Mettre une pagaille pareille,
It's you!
Je parle de toi,
Aokiji!
Aokiji !
My crew is frozen solid outside!
Mes hommes sont gelés à l’entrée. Mets fin à ton pouvoir.
You're annoying me.
Mets-la en veilleuse.
And don't even think about using your power.
Oublie tout de suite le Fruit du Tremblement.
Your crew will shatter and die.
Tes petits copains se casseraient.
You're their captain, so I think you know.
T’es leur capitaine. Tu les connais.
Do you really think I started it?
Tu crois que j’ai ouvert les hostilités ?
Besides, you already know, don't you?
Ne viens pas me dire que t’es pas au courant.
I'm not just heartbroken, I'm furious.
Non seulement je suis blessé, mais en plus, j’ai la rage.
Take a guess who actually started this.
Qui est en tort, à ton avis ?
Another round over here!
Ça manque de gnôle !
You can really knock 'em back, Ice Pop!
T’as une sacrée descente, glace à l’eau !
You're not bad yourself, you son of a bitch!
Tu peux parler, espèce d’ordure.
So what did Akainu say next?
Et qu’est-ce qu’il a dit, alors, Akainu ?
"Two men who enlisted the same year in a fight to the death...
Que ce combat à mort entre deux camarades
My eyes are burning with tears."
ne le laissait pas de glace.
And I said, "Yeah, that's 'cause...
Ça risquait pas,
your magma's flowing!"
ce fumier est en magma !
And now look at me!
Regardez le résultat.
I'm down to one leg!
J’ai perdu une jambe.
So that's what happens when two admirals fight!
Ça rigole pas, les duels entre Amiraux.
What about Akainu?
Et Akainu, dans tout ça ? Tu lui as arraché un bras ?
No...
Non.
But I'm sure he's scarred to all hell.
Mais il avait le corps couvert de cicatrices.
Speaking of scars, he might know Burn Scar, Commodore.
En parlant de ça, tu connaîtrais pas l’homme à la cicatrice de feu ?
There are four important red lode poneglyphs in the world.
Dans le monde,
Big Mom and Kaido have two of them...
Kaido et Big Mom ont pris possession de deux d’entre eux.
But we can't find the other two!
Ça en fait deux restants.
Once more fate rears its head...
Ce sera une question de chance.
Yeah...
Oui.
And they say that the Man with the Burn Scar has one of them.
L’un d’eux
Is it me?
Moi, peut-être ?
You just got that scar, you idiot!
Tu viens de te la faire, ta cicatrice !
Rumor has it...
D’après la rumeur,
that he sails a pitch-black ship.
cet homme naviguerait sur un navire d’ébène.
And when you get close, he creates a giant whirlpool to swallow you up.
Quand on l’approche,
He may have eaten a devil fruit...
Il a sûrement mangé un Fruit du démon.
I believe he works for the government.
Pour moi, c’est un gaillard du Gouvernement.
The World Government has dark secrets, after all.
Le Gouvernement Mondial est nimbé de mystère.
If they hold on to even one of the stones,
S’ils gardent une des pierres,
it means that no pirate will ever reach the One Piece, the single greatest hidden treasure.
les pirates peuvent oublier le trésor qui les lie tous.
The poneglyphs... I only have bitter memories involving them.
Les Ponéglyphes ? J’en ai que des mauvais souvenirs.
If I saw a red stone like that in Ohara, I'd remember it.
Si j’avais vu une pierre rouge et rutilante sur Ohara,
All I can remember...
Tout ce dont je me souvienne,
is a good friend who rebelled against the government...
c’est mon ami en rébellion contre le Gouvernement
and a girl with eyes full of despair...
et les yeux emplis de tristesse
whose fate was in my hands.
de la jeune fille dont le destin était dans mes mains.
What kind of boring story is that?!
T’as fini de nous faire chialer ?
Commodore, what should we do?
Que fait-on, amiral ?
If we take his power for ourselves, it'll be a considerable asset to us...
Voler ses pouvoirs ajouterait une belle corde à notre arc.
I heard that, you slimy bastards!
Je vous entends, bande de déchets.
How about I send you to an icy hell?!
Je vous mets un aller simple pour le monde des glaçons ?
Stop, stop, stop!
Non, fais pas ça !
That's right, I've already heard about you guys hunting devil fruit powers.
Maintenant que vous le dites,
Bring it on!
Je vous attends de pied ferme !
Wait!
Un petit instant !
I'm sorry!
Excuse-les.
What my crew member said was ridiculous.
Ils ne savent pas ce qu’ils disent.
I wouldn't dream of doing that.
Je te veux aucun mal, tu sais.
What I really wanted to ask you was...
Au contraire, en vrai.
Do you wanna sail with us?
Et si tu rejoignais mon équipage ?
You lost your position, didn't you?
Tu es libre, en ce moment.
Do you have a place to go?
Où tu comptes aller ? Tu sais déjà quoi faire ?
The guardians of justice have abandoned you!
La justice t’a prié de partir.
Man, this must be rock bottom.
Je suis tombé bien bas,
A pirate worrying about my prospects.
si même un pirate s’inquiète pour moi…
Wherever you go, whatever you do,
Où que tu ailles et quoi que tu fasses,
trouble will always find you!
tu finiras mêlé à une guerre.
So what flag are you gonna fight under?
Quand tu te battras,
Huh?!
Je peux savoir ?
I'm different from the Marines!
Je n’ai rien à voir avec ces bouffons de la Marine.
I have my own brand of justice!
La justice est différente, en mon monde.
Don't be stupid!
Pauvre tanche !
Just because we shared a few drinks doesn't mean I trust scum like you!
Boire de la gnôle avec vous,
I think you have the wrong idea about pirates.
Tu te fais des films sur les pirates, mon gars.
It's not like we're all buddies here!
On n’est pas une bande de potes qui voyage ensemble.
The only thing a pirate crew needs...
Entre pirates, mon gars,
is to have mutual interests!
on fait équipe car c’est dans notre intérêt.
You're free now...
T’es libre de toute attache, non ?
so what do you wanna do?
Quel avenir tu veux ?
Hey, Kuzan!
Kuzan !
Thaw out Hibari!
Dégèle Hibari !
Let Koby escape!
Laisse partir Kobby !
Come back to the Marines!
Et reviens dans la Marine !
You haven't changed at all. Always saying what's on your mind.
Comme d’hab, tu dis tout haut ce qui te passe par la tête.
But I can't let any of that happen, Garp!
Je ne peux pas t’offrir ce que tu me demandes, Garp.
I've always loved...
Tu es un homme libre.
how straightforward you are...
J’ai toujours aimé ça chez toi.
which is why I'm living the way I want to now!
Moi aussi, aujourd’hui, je vis comme je l’entends.
Kuzan Captain of the Tenth Ship Blackbeard Pirates
Kuzan Commandant du 10e navire de Barbe Noire
Bonehead...
Sombre imbécile…
Ice...
Ice...
Ball!
Ball !
Vice Admiral Garp!
Vice-amiral Garp !
In order to save your beloved protégé,
Pour sauver ton disciple bien-aimé,
can you kill your former star pupil?!
oseras-tu tuer ton ancien meilleur disciple ?
Don't live in the past, you moron!
Ne sois pas prisonnier du passé.
I taught you to live in the moment!
Je t’ai appris à vivre dans le présent !
It didn't work!
Ça lui fait rien !
Listen, Kuzan!
Écoute-moi bien, Kuzan.
Wavering is a sign...
Hésiter est un signe…
of weakness!
de faiblesse !
Blue Hole!
Blue Hole !
Meanwhile, at Winner Island...
Au même moment, sur Winner Island…
Winner Island New World
Winner Island Nouveau Monde
You can hardly call yourself a pirate crew without a ship!
Difficile de prétendre être un pirate sans un navire pour son équipage.
There's no way for you to escape!
Vous êtes pris au piège.
The hundred pirates whose hearts you stole at Rocky Port...
Les cent pirates à qui tu as piqué le cœur
are still living in fear on the Pirate Island!
vivent toujours dans la peur sur l’île des pirates.
But if I bring them your heart, they're sure to raise a toast!
Si je leur ramène le tien,
You really made it for me!
Tu as préparé ces boules pour moi ?
But I can't guarantee it'll work.
Oui, mais je ne garantis pas qu’elles fonctionnent.
Now...
Que faire ?
I'm having a hard time deciding whether to sell or use the Op-Op Fruit.
Vendre le Fruit du Bistouri ou s’en servir ? Dilemme.
It can even grant me eternal youth, can't it?!
À moins qu’on me rende immortel ?
Get your hands...
Pas touche…
off my captain!
à mon capitaine !
Bepo...
Bepo…
What?! Sulong?!
Hein ? Un Sulong ?
No way! The moon isn't even out!
Impossible. La lune n’est pas de sortie !
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Du calme, p’tit gars !
Captain!
Capitaine !
Dammit! They fled to sea!
Bon sang, il s’est tiré dans l’océan !
Don't let him get away!
Chopez-le-moi !
Go back, Bepo...
Retourne sur la terre ferme, Bepo…
I can't... leave the crew... behind...
Je ne peux pas… abandonner mes frères d’armes…
I won't go back!
Hors de question !
Trust them, Captain!
Fais-nous confiance, capitaine.
From that frigid northern port all the way until now...
Depuis notre départ, dans ce port gelé au nord…
we've always survived!
on en a bavé tous ensemble.
So...
Croyez-moi…
none of us will die here!
personne ne mourra !
We've overcome so much together!
On a surmonté les plus dures épreuves.
So, Captain!
Capitaine, pitié…
Don't die!
reste en vie !
Please...
Je t’en supplie…
don't die!
Ne meurs pas !
At Winner Island in the New World...
Ainsi, dans le Nouveau Monde, sur Winner Island,
the Heart Pirates' submarine, the Polar Tang,
le Polar Tang, navire sous-marin de l’équipage du Heart,
was sunk.
coula par le fond.
The Heart Pirates led by Trafalgar Law...
Quant à l’équipage proprement dit, commandé par Trafalgaw Law…
were defeated.
il fut défait.